bizquest.com 2015-06-07

# Business for Sale | Buy A Business or Sell A Business | Privacy Statement - BizQuest.com

[Home](http://www.bizquest.com/) > **Privacy Policy**

Last Updated: January 5, 2015 

BizQuest has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's Program Requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, www.bizquest.com does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile applications. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. When you visit a web site displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, you can expect to be notified of the following information 

  * The personal information collected and which organization is collecting the information 
  * How the information is used and with whom the information may be shared 
  * Choices available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  * Types of security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company's control 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

Questions regarding this statement can be submitted via this [contact form](http://www.bizquest.com/support/contact.aspx "Contact Form"). Alternatively, please contact us by mail at BizQuest Administration -- Privacy Statement, 2100 E. Route 66, Suite 200, Glendora, CA 91740, or by telephone at 888-280-3815.   
If the web site has not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint "Businesses for sale on BizQuest"). For more information on TRUSTe, please go to [http://www.truste.com](http://www.truste.org/ "TRUSTe"). 

##  **BizQuest's Privacy Statement**

BizQuest, is wholly owned subsidiary of CoStar Group (collectively "CoStar", "we", "us" or "our") provide this Privacy Statement that covers the website [http://www.BizQuest.com/](http://www.bizquest.com/ "Franchises for sale on BizQuest"). By accessing, using or registering with BizQuest's web site, you accept and agree to BizQuest's Privacy Statement. BizQuest provides a variety of online services to assist individuals and brokers with buying and selling businesses and franchises. BizQuest values your privacy, feedback and candor very highly. Any user information we collect is considered private and we do not use it or share it except as permitted herein, without the user's permission. We use this personal information at BizQuest to provide the best quality service possible. The following privacy statement summarizes BizQuest's protection and use of any personal information provided by visitors to the BizQuest site. 

This statement does not apply to any public area of BizQuest's web site or services. In the event you submit personal information to contact another member, contact a lister about a listing, create a listing, add a contact on a listing, the BizQuest Blog or Broker Directory, such information becomes publicly available and BizQuest is not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit to these services, forums, listings, or persons. 

**Information Collected by BizQuest:**

BizQuest collects user information from several areas of the BizQuest site including products; business services; the adding and editing of business and franchise listings; the adding and editing of Broker Directory Listings; email forms; the BizQuest Blog; and any surveys or contests that BizQuest may sponsor. BizQuest collects individual user search activity for statistical, archival, and business purposes. BizQuest collects financial information (such as billing address, credit card number, expiration date) for billing payment and credit card authorization purposes. BizQuest may track the IP address of a user's computer or place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. This is required by BizQuest services to provide automated features. 

**Use of Information Collected:**

Collected information helps BizQuest better understand its users' needs in order to improve its product and service offerings. Email addresses are used to communicate with members through the BizQuest Buyer, Broker and Franchise Newsletters (weekly or bi-weekly email news summaries); Promotional emails; Partner emails and for site administration purposes. Users may be deleted from LoopNews, Promotional email and Partner email lists at their request. Personal information may be used to contact users for the purpose of research, product development, marketing, or customer service, if the user has opted to receive such communication. User search activity is collected and analyzed and may be utilized by BizQuest in the aggregate or in the abstract for a variety of business purposes. Financial information is used to bill users for products and services purchased. Within BizQuest, only accounting managers have access to the credit card account information. This information is not shared with anyone outside of BizQuest. IP address and cookie log data is analyzed to better understand traffic flows and user preferences. BizQuest may retain the data it collects indefinitely. You may have your personal information deleted or deactivated by sending an email to [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com). You may be asked to confirm your identity. You will receive a response within 10 business days. 

**Use of Email Tools:**

You may NOT use the Email the Broker, Email a Listing service or other email services that we offer to send spam (i.e. unsolicited commercial email) or otherwise send content that would violate BizQuest's Terms and Conditions. We may monitor, track or save the use of this feature, but will be under no obligation to monitor, track or save these email messages sent from these tools. If you send an email using the Email a Listing to a Friend service to an email address that is not registered in our system, we do not use that email address for any purpose other than to send your email, and for us to automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. BizQuest stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and for tracking the success of our referral program. We also do not rent or sell these email addresses of un-registered users. 

Your friend may contact us at [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

**Shared information:**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

These companies are authorized to use your personally identifiable information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

Though BizQuest makes every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request served on our website and to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

BizQuest shares member information in the following areas on the site: Business and Franchise Listing Service, Saved Search Email Alerts, BizQuest Blog and the Broker Directory. When a member enters a business or franchise listing in the Listing Service, listing contact information is also entered. In addition, members searching BizQuest can view contact information when they view a listing profile. BizQuest allows users to share contact information with one another via its Saved Search Email Alert service. With Saved Searches users can save their business search criteria to have information about businesses that match the specified criteria emailed to them. When selecting this service, users are given the option of releasing their contact information to other users who have business listings that match their criteria. This contact information is then shared with the users who have business listings that match the buying or leasing criteria. Unless required by law as detailed in this section or a user specifically takes action as discussed in this paragraph, BizQuest does not share individual user search activity information and such activity information remains private to the individual user and to BizQuest. Broker Members agree to share their contact information and allow all BizQuest users to view their contact information via the BizQuest Business Broker Directory or via links made available to users on a listing or in an email. BizQuest users who do not opt out of the Broker Directory service during registration with BizQuest (or anytime thereafter) also agree to share their contact information via the BizQuest Broker Directory. 

BizQuest shares information with its partners for the purpose of providing related services in which we deem our users have interest. The use that BizQuest's partners make of customer information will not exceed BizQuest's use of the data. Key billing information (such as credit card number, expiration date and dollar amount) gathered from users making online purchases of products or services is shared with PayPal or CyberSource, our credit card processing partners, in order to authorize charges to the credit card. BizQuest also uses third party providers to perform email and postal mailings on behalf of BizQuest, but this information (such as name, address and email) is confidential and is not used by the provider for any other purpose. 

BizQuest does not rent or lease user information to any third party, except as disclosed here. From time to time, BizQuest may obtain information (such as electronic mail addresses) from third party providers. It is our goal to only contact individuals who we believe may have a legitimate business interest in BizQuest based on their membership or participation in other organizations or web sites, and who have indicated a willingness to be contacted for this purpose. While BizQuest endeavors to work with other sites and companies with a similar respect for user privacy, BizQuest cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. 

Please be aware that BizQuest was recently acquired by CoStar Group, Inc. ("CoStar"), and as a result all BizQuest customer information, including personal, company and listing information, has been and will be shared with CoStar. Please be aware that in the event CoStar and/or BizQuest merges with a third party, or in the event all or substantially all of CoStar's and/or BizQuest's assets are acquired by a third party, customer information, including personal, company and listing information, will be shared and/or transferred to such third party. The information may only be used or shared by such third parties for the primary purpose for which the information was originally collected. If such third parties, or if BizQuest for its own business needs, desire to use the personal information for another purpose, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information prior to the information being used for a new purpose, and you will have the opportunity to opt out of such new use of your personal information. 

**Security of personal information:**

BizQuest's clients and their personal information are considered to be BizQuest's greatest asset and thus their privacy is treated with the utmost regard and respect. BizQuest takes every reasonable precaution to secure personal information within both its computers and its physical premises. 

The security of your personal information is important to BizQuest. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). [To learn more about SSL, follow this link [http://www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/ "VeriSign")]. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, please [contact us](http://www.bizquest.com/support/contact.aspx "Contact Us"). 

**Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by BizQuest and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

**Log Files**

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. 

**Local Storage**

We use Local Storage (LS) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LS such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LS. 

**Behavioral Advertising**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/ "Opt Out"). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

**Testimonials**

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personal information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent to post their name along with their testimonial prior to any posting of such testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from these testimonials, contact us at [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why? 

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Twitter button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it. 

**Collection and Use of Third Party Personal Information**

You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name, physical address, email address and etc. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided. 

**Links to 3rd Party Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of BizQuest. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

**Public Member Directory**

We will list you in our publicly accessible member directory. If you wish to request removal of your information from our directory, you can contact us at [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com). 

**Opting-out, editing, updating or deleting personal information:**

BizQuest utilizes email as a vital and primary communication channel with registered users and customers. As a registered user/customer, you hereby acknowledge and grant BizQuest the permission to communicate with you via email (as well as other communication channels such as phone and fax) for any purposes BizQuest determines to be relevant including, but not limited to, system messages, product updates, service announcements and other marketing messages. BizQuest will use best efforts to honor customers request to opt out of marketing messages, but under no circumstances will BizQuest have any liability for sending any email to its registered users/customers. 

Users who do not wish to receive marketing emails including the BizQuest Newsletters, BizQuest Promotional Emails, or Sponsor Emails are requested to contact [BizQuest Client Services](http://www.bizquest.com/support/contact.aspx "BizQuest Client Services"), or select the opt-out option that is available on all email correspondence. Additionally, users may also opt out of Saved Search Email Alerts by returning to the Saved Search section and clicking on the "Remove this Search" button. We also send our users site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about service notices and responsibilities. BizQuest occasionally communicates with its users via email and phone to provide information about requested services and regarding issues related to their account. It is important to note that this communication is not used for marketing or promotional purposes. Requesting the deletion of certain types of user information may prevent users from accessing some web site features. 

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, delete or update your personal information by making the change on your member profile page or by emailing our Customer Support at [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

Subscriptions will automatically renew using the Customer's current credit card account number unless Customer cancels their subscription on the BizQuest Web site at http://www.BizQuest.com/myaccount/ three (3) days prior to the renewal date to cancel such subscription. All cancellation requests will be processed within five (5) business days. Once the cancellation is processed, a confirmation email will be sent via the customer's email account on record with BizQuest. If Customer has a question about a cancellation, Customer should contact [BizQuest Client Services](http://www.bizquest.com/support/contact.aspx "Contact Us") at [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com) or at 888-280-3815. The Company reserves the right to change its fees or billing methods at any time. The Company will provide timely notice to the affected Customers of any such changes. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Notification Procedures:**

BizQuest may provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice (including via fax), or through posting of such notice on our website, as determined by BizQuest in our sole discretion. BizQuest reserves the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to our users, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described herein.  BizQuest is not responsible for any automatic filtering you or your network provider may apply to email notifications we send to the email address you provide us.  We recommend that you add [bizquestcs@bizquest.com](mailto:bizquestcs@bizquest.com) to your email address book to help ensure you receive email notifications from us. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement:**

If BizQuest decides to change its privacy statement, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

BizQuest reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If BizQuest makes material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
